nbad.com 2016-08-10

# NBAD Privacy Policy

**Introduction**  
National Bank of Abu Dhabi PJSC and its affiliates (“NBAD”) are committed to providing the highest level of privacy and security regarding collection and use of their customers’ personal information by the NBAD websites. This policy describes how we may collect, use and disclose your personal information including when contacting us or using nbad.com and our related websites (“NBAD Websites”).

Personal information comprises all the details NBAD holds or collects directly or indirectly (including via cookies or other similar tools) about you, your transactions, financial information, interactions or dealings with NBAD, including information received from third parties and information collected through use of our websites and our electronic banking services.

Use of the NBAD Websites is subject to [our terms of use](https://www.nbad.com/en-ae/utility-and-legal/terms-and-conditions.html) and any products and services supplied are subject to [our terms and conditions](https://www.nbad.com/en-ae/utility-and-legal/terms-and-conditions.html).  
If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy or the security of your personal information, please contact us on [AskSecurity@nbad.com](mailto:AskSecurity@nbad.com).  
For more information about our use of cookies please refer to [our Cookie Policy](https://www.nbad.com/en-ae/utility-and-legal/cookie-policy.html).

**Handling personal information**  
Purposes for which NBAD may handle your personal information include the following:

  * Processing applications for products and services, effecting payments, transactions and completing instructions or requests.  

  * Providing products and services (including electronic banking services).
  * Assessing customer suitability for products and services.
  * Credit assessments, including conducting credit checks and setting credit limits.
  * Establishment, continuation and management of banking relationships and accounts.
  * Conducting market research and surveys with the aim of improving our products and services.
  * For marketing purposes and promotions.
  * For the prevention, detection, investigation and prosecution of crime (including without limitation, money laundering, terrorism, fraud and other financial crime) in any jurisdiction, identity verification, government sanctions screening and due diligence checks.
  * To comply with local or foreign law, regulations, voluntary codes, directives, judgements or court orders, agreements between any member of the NBAD group and any authority, regulator or enforcement agency policies, reporting requirements under financial transaction legislation and demands or requests of any authority, regulator, enforcement agency or exchange body.
  * To seek professional advice, including in connection with any legal proceedings (including any prospective legal proceedings) for obtaining legal advice or establishing, exercising or defending legal rights.
  * Surveillance of premises and ATMs.

**Disclosure of personal information**  
We allow third party service providers to process personal information where this is needed in connection with a service they provide NBAD. These arrangements may involve your personal information being located in various countries around the world including the United Arab Emirates where NBAD has its head office.  
You should be aware that different privacy laws may apply in these countries from any laws that may apply in the country where you are located. NBAD will always strive to adopt the highest standards of privacy protection wherever your personal information is located.  
Our privacy policy does not apply to third-party websites where our online advertisements are displayed or to linked third-party websites which we do not operate or control.

**Monitoring**  
To the extent permitted by law, NBAD may record and monitor your communications with us to ensure compliance with our legal and regulatory obligations and our internal policies. This may include the recording of telephone conversations.

**Right of Access**  
Subject to applicable law, regulations and/or banking industry guidelines, you may have the right to request a copy of the personal information processed in relation to you. NBAD may be allowed, by law, to charge a fee for providing you with a copy of your personal information.  
To request a copy of your personal information, please contact us on [AskSecurity@nbad.com](mailto:AskSecurity@nbad.com).

**Security**  
The security of your personal information is important to us and NBAD has invested significant resources to protect the safekeeping and confidentiality of your personal information. When using external service providers, we require that they adhere to the same standards as NBAD. Personal information may be transferred or stored at a location outside of your country of residence. Regardless of where personal information is transferred or stored, we take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that personal information is kept secure.

The Internet is not a secure form of communication and sending and receiving information over the Internet carries with it risks including the risk of access and interference by unauthorized third parties. Information passing over the Internet may be transmitted internationally (even when the sender and recipient are located in the same country) via countries with weaker privacy and data protection laws than your country of residence.  
We do not accept responsibility or liability for the confidentiality, security or integrity of your personal information in connection with its transmission over the Internet.

**Social media**  
NBAD operates channels, pages and accounts on some social media sites to inform, assist and engage with customers. We monitor and record comments and posts made on these channels about NBAD so that we can improve our services.  
NBAD is not responsible for any information posted on those sites other than information we have posted ourselves. We do not endorse the social media sites themselves or any information posted on them by third parties.

When you engage with NBAD via social media, your personal information may be stored on that social media site’s servers which are outside the control of NBAD and may be held in the United States of America or elsewhere in the world. Any information posted to such sites may be accessed and read by the general public. NBAD will not ask you to share personal, account or security information via social media sites and you should not post such information on these channels.

**Changes to this privacy policy**  
NBAD may in its absolute discretion update this privacy policy from time to time. It is therefore recommended that you review it regularly.
